(Bernadette:)What you doing?
You said clean up. I'm cleaning up, heh.
(Bernadette:)You can't just throw everything
in the closet.
(Howard:)You can tell me what to do
or you can tell me how to do it...
(Howard:)...but you can't do both.
This isn't sex.
Well, what if someone looks in there?
They're coming over for dinner,
no one will look in the closet.
(Bernadette:)You don't know that. What if someone's
looking for the bathroom?
It could work out.
(Howard:)For all we know,
there's a toilet in there somewhere.
Fine. After tonight,
we need to get a handle on this mess.
(Howard:)We should show the closet to Sheldon.
(Bernadette:)Why?
Ha. Are you kidding?
He's like a savant at organizing.
(Howard:)Everything in his apartment
has a label on it...
(Howard:)...including his label maker,
which has a label that says "label maker."
If you look really close at that label-maker
label, you'll see a label that says "label."
No, he's our guest. We can't ask him
to straighten our closet.
(Howard:)No, we wouldn't ask him.